Your cart is empty
------------------

Have an account?

[Log in](https://www.livpure.com/account/login) to check out faster.

Your cart
---------

Loading...

Order special instructions Order special instructions

Subtotal
--------

₹0.00

Tax included. [Shipping](https://www.livpure.com/policies/shipping-policy) calculated at checkout.

Update

Check out

Snapmint | 0% EMI | available above ₹2999

* Customer Support

* Water Purifiers
    
    Water Purifiers
    
    * RO on Rent
        
        RO on Rent

* Mattress
    
    Mattress

* Bedding
    
    Bedding

* Appliances
    
    Appliances

* Buy ACMC
    
    Buy ACMC

* Water Purifiers
    
    * RO on Rent

* Mattress

* Bedding

* Appliances

* Buy ACMC

Deals 

 Search [Log in](https://www.livpure.com/account/login) [Cart](https://www.livpure.com/cart)

Updated on 09-July-2024
=======================

##### 1.INTRODUCTION

1.1 LIVPURE is committed to ensuring privacy of the Users on its website (“Website”) and/or mobile application (“Mobile App”). In furtherance of the same, LIVPURE has framed this Privacy Policy in accordance with the Information Technology Act, 2000 (“Act”) read with the applicable Rules thereunder.

1.2 The Privacy Policy is designed to familiarize Users of this Website / Mobile App with (a) the type of information that Users may share with LIVPURE, or that LIVPURE will collect from the Users; (b) practices and policies of LIVPURE relating to collection, storage, dealing, transfer, disclosure, transfer etc. of information pertaining to Users; (c) purpose of collection and usage of such information, and related matters.

1.3 This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use of the Website / Mobile App.

##### 2\. IMPORTANT TERMS

2.1 Please read the terms of this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy, along with the “Terms of Use” constitute an “electronic record” in the form of an “electronic contract” as defined under the Information Technology Act, 2000 between LIVPURE and the User of this Website / Mobile App. This Privacy Policy does not require any physical, electronic or digital signature.

2.2 This Privacy Policy forms an integral part of the “Terms of Use” of the Website / Mobile App. If You do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website / Mobile App. By visiting this Website / using the Mobile App, you (a) unconditionally accept, and agree to be bound by the “Terms of Use” of the Website/ Mobile App, read with this Privacy Policy; and (b) expressly consent to the collection, receipt, possession, storage, usage, dealing, handling or transfer of Your personal information by LIVPURE in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

2.3 The Privacy Policy can undergo a change at any time at the discretion of LIVPURE. Therefore, it is suggested that You regularly check the Website / Mobile App to be apprised of the latest changes made to the Privacy Policy.

##### 3\. TYPES OF USER INFORMATION

3.1 Collection of “Information”: LIVPURE may request for, collect or gather such “Information” (which shall include data) as it deems necessary, relevant or incidental for rendering an improved shopping experience to Users and for other purposes as specified in Paragraph 6 below.

3.2 Personal Information: Such “Information” may include Personal Information relating to Users such as (a) User’s name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, postal address, delivery address (if different), gender, purchase history etc. (b) financial information such as bank account or credit or debit card information; (c) physical condition of User; (d) a description of the item requested or purchased; (e) the internet protocol (“IP”) address of User’s computer; (f) any other “sensitive personal data or information” relating to the User as defined under the applicable Rules under the Act.

3.3 Non-personal Information LIVPURE may also collect certain non-personal Information from the User, when the User visits and / or uses the Website / Mobile App. Such non-personal Information would include but not be limited to information such as geographical location of User, IP address, type of browser, operating system of User’s device, and details of usage of Website / Mobile App etc. Such non-personal Information is collected through various ways including “cookies”. Cookies are text files placed on Your computer, to help the Website / Mobile App analyse how You use the Website / Mobile App. Such information is not used to track information about individuals, but is used on an aggregate level to customize our site, improve the online experience of the User and plan advertising and promotions.

3.4 Cookies, Web Beacons and Tracking Codes: Cookies are small text files that a website downloads onto your computer or other internet-enabled devices (such as mobile phones and tablets) when you visit a website. The cookie will help the Website / Mobile App recognise your device the next time you visit. We may use both session cookies (disappear after you close your browser) and persistent cookies (remain after you close your browser and may be accessed every time you use or connect to our Website / Mobile App). We may collect information like user’s IP address, geographical location, browser/device type and version, operating system, referral source, device, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of user website use through "cookies". You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allow you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies), you may not be able to access all or parts of our site, or they may not function properly.

##### 4.MODES OF COLLECTION OF USER INFORMATION

4.1 The information referred to above may be collected or received by LIVPURE (a) directly from the User, when the User either provides any specific information on the Website / Mobile App; or (b) from use of the Website / Mobile App by the User (including through IoT device placed in the LIVPURE product purchased by the User); or (c) from third parties who have collected any Information relating to the User, and who have shared it with LIVPURE.

4.2 There are times when You may provide information to us voluntarily, otherwise than through use of the Website / Mobile App. This occurs when You provide Your feedback to us through e-mails, return forms, letters or telephone calls. We may use this information to respond to Your query and to keep track of feedback received from You.

##### 5.PURPOSE OF COLLECTION AND USAGE OF INFORMATION

LIVPURE may collect, store and use Information for any purpose as may be permissible under Applicable Laws, including but limited to the following:

* (a) To display the User’s business listing or Product offerings across the Website / Mobile App to fetch maximum business opportunities for the User;
* (b) Facilitation of Your use of the Website / Mobile App, handling and execution of orders placed on the Website / Mobile App by the User, process payments, communication with User about orders etc.;
* (c) Respond to any inquiries posed by the User;
* (d) Provide User with details of important schemes, offers, Product details, new Product launches, changes to terms of use of the Website / Mobile App, order details, delivery details and make other important announcements etc. ;
* (e) Maintain accounts of the User, display contents inputted by User such as User profile, User wishlist etc.;
* (f) Help recommend to the User merchandise and services that may be of interest to him / her;
* (g) Personalize User’s experience on the Website / Mobile App by presenting advertisements, Products and offers tailored to the User’s preferences;
* (h) Customization, administration etc. of the Website / Mobile App, location of errors, Website / Mobile App testing, data analysis for the Website etc;
* (i) Provision of various services on the Website / Mobile App;
* (j) To protect integrity of the Website / Mobile App, improve our platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuse of our Website / Mobile App;
* (k) To conduct analytical studies on various aspects including User behaviour, User preferences etc.
* (l) Enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf;
* (m) To permit employees of the Company to contact Users, and enable them to implement the orders placed by Users, resolve User queries, issues, grievances etc.;
* (n) To further improve the product and/or services, to facilitate the servicing of User’s product and/or to give insight on User’s product experience.
* (o) To trace computer resources of any person for the purposes of determining compliance with the provisions of the Information

Technology Act, 2000 and / or any other law for the time being in force.

##### 6.DISCLOSURE AND RETENTION OF USER INFORMATION

6.1 LIVPURE considers the Information about its customers as an important part of its business. Accordingly, LIVPURE shall not engage in sale of Information relating to Users to third parties. However, LIVPURE may share User information with third parties in the circumstances specified herein below, after reasonably assuring itself that such third parties have undertaken to maintain confidentiality of Personal Information relating to the Users:

* (a) Third Party Vendors / Service Providers etc.: Personal Information relating to Users may be made available to the third party Vendors, distributors etc. who sell their Products on the Website / Mobile App. Further, LIVPURE may engage third party service providers to render various services, and perform various functions in relation to the business undertaken on the Website / Mobile App, and / or for the Purpose(s) discussed in Paragraph 6 above. For instance, LIVPURE may engage third party service providers for maintenance of its Website / Mobile App, fulfilment of orders, delivery of packages, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing of credit card payments, provision of customer services etc. Such third party service providers / Vendors would have access to Personal Information of Users for the purpose of performing their functions / rendering their services etc.
* (b) Business Transfers: LIVPURE may transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Your Information in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or business or in the event of bankruptcy. Should such a sale or transfer occur, LIVPURE will reasonably ensure that the Information You have provided and which we have collected is stored and used by the transferee in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Any third party to which LIVPURE transfers or sells as aforesaid will have the right to continue to use the information that You provide to us or collected by us immediately prior to the transfer.
* (c) Government Agency: LIVPURE may share any Information relating to Users (i) with Government agencies mandated under the law to obtain Information relating to Users from LIVPURE; (ii) any third party, when LIVPURE is required to disclose the same under an order of a government or judicial authority under any law for the time being in force, or where such disclosure is necessary for the compliance of a legal obligation.
* (d) With User Consent: Without prejudice to the aforesaid, LIVPURE may disclose Personal Information relating to the User with his / her / its consent. For this purpose, LIVPURE may send a prior notice to the User before sharing Personal Information relating to the User with third parties. In case no objection or intimation is received from the User, LIVPURE would presume that User has granted its consent for sharing of said Information with third parties.

By using or visiting the Website / Mobile App and agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, User shall be construed to have consented to, and accepted the disclosure of his Information to third parties as provided under this Privacy Policy.

6.2 LIVPURE will share Your Personal Information internally with such persons who need it to complete Your purchase or carry out Your instructions regarding the receipt of marketing information.

6.3 LIVPURE shall keep sensitive personal data or information for only as long as the purposes for which the information may lawfully be used or is otherwise required under any other law for the time being in force. For those customers who have registered for the mailing list, their personal information is kept until we are notified that they no longer want their information stored.

##### 7.SECURITY PRACTICES AND PROCEDURES FOR PROTECTION OF INFORMATION

In order to make every effort to ensure that Your experience on the Website / Mobile App is secure, we use encryption technology to protect You against the loss, misuse or alteration of Your personal information. When You fill out any contact forms or access Your account, a secure server encrypts all of Your information through the use of Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). To be sure You are browsing secure pages for transactions, check Your Web browser’s status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in Your web browser to tell You that You are viewing a secure web page. Also, all browsers display an “s” after the “http” (https://) in the Web site address to indicate that You are in a secure environment.

##### 8.ACCURACY AND PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

LIVPURE relies on Users to notify it of any changes in personal information. Should any inaccurate information come to LIVPURE’s attention, it will investigate and correct the information and, if necessary, apprise the User of the change. Only those staff members who need the User’s personal information in order to respond to the User’s requests are given access to it. Employees are provided with training and information regarding the proper handling of personal information. All information stored in LIVPURE’s computer system is protected from unauthorized access and information that is stored in document form is kept in secure locations to prevent access by unauthorized persons.

##### 9\. USER DISCRETION AND THE CHOICE TO OPT OUT

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allow you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies), you may not be able to access all or parts of our site, or they may not function properly. The Users have a choice to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing related) communications from us, after setting up an account.

In order to remove Your contact information, please visit Unsubscribe.

##### 10\. GRIEVANCE OFFICER

In compliance with Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made thereunder, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:  
**Name**: Livpure Smart Homes Private Limited  
**Address**: 221, PHASE – 1, UDYOG VIHAR, GURGAON, HARYANA – 122016  
**Phone**: +91-124 403 5614

**Grievance Officer**: Prashant Agarwal  
**Email**: [grievances.officer@sar-group.com](mailto:grievances.officer@sar-group.com)  
**Time**: 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM  

##### 11. UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may periodically update the Privacy Policy. Please refer the Updated on legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on our Website / Mobile App. Your use of the Website / Mobile App following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.

##### 12\. GOVERNING LAW

The Website and Mobile App are designed and targeted to users who reside in the Republic of India and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the India. By accessing and/or providing personal information through the Website / Mobile App, you confirm that you meet the legal requirements for disclosure of personal information in your jurisdiction.

**Sales**

* For Sales : [+91 9121230397](tel:+919121230397)
* For Rental RO:  [+91 8800762226](tel:+918800762226)

**Support**

* For Service : [080648-99399](tel:08064899399)

×

Livpure Cookies Policy
======================

Livpure will collect and use your personal data for making your product booking and for providing the services you request. During this process, we may record your preferences as well as the information about any issues you encountered during your product. Our only objective of doing this is to better meet and exceed your needs during subsequent purchasing.  
We may disclose your information to our service providers for analytical purposes so that we can better improvise your buying experience and our website facilities. Livpure has agreements to ensure confidentiality of all such information shared with service providers we work with for this purpose.  
Your personal data is kept secure. Only authorized employees, business partners, clients, contractors and other third-party providers (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.  
Livpure shall retain personal data only as long as necessary for the fulfilment of the stated purposes and should be disposed thereafter. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Please tick the boxes for your consent to the use of following personal data:

*  KYC
*  Product enhancement market feedback
*  Cookie policies
*  Customer experience
*  Support and shipping related services

All the information you give is voluntary. You have the legal right to apply for a copy of the information we hold on you and correct any inaccuracies as well as object to its use.  
You may review, update, correct or delete your personal data by e-mailing us at customercare@livpure.com. You may at any time also, contact our Data Protection Officer directly with questions and suggestions concerning data protection by e-mailing us at grievance.officer@sar-group.com  
For a full description on how we process and keep safe your personal data, please see our Privacy Policy at: [Privacy Policy](https://livpure.com/policies/privacy-policy)

Save & Continue

 By creating an account on Livpure, you agree to our [Privacy Policy](https://livpure.com/policies/privacy-policy), receive WhatsApp, SMS notifications or Call and consent to our cookie policy.

#### Products

#### Follow Us

#### Resources

#### Water Purifier in Your City

#### Registered Office

* **Registered Address**  
    Livpure Smart Homes Pvt Ltd, Plot No 221, Udhyog Vihar Phase 1, Gurgaon, Haryana, 122016 India
* **Manufacturer and Packer**  
    Plot No 39, Sector 4, IMT Manesar, Gurgaon, Haryana, 122050, India

#### Support & Policies

#### Sales & Services

* For Sales : [+91 9121230397](tel:+919121230397)
* For Rental RO : [+91 8800762226](tel:+918800762226)
* RO Customer Care Services : [080648-99399](tel:08064899399)
Sleep : care@livpuresleep.com  
Appliances : customercare@livpure.com  
Rental RO : care@livpuresmart.com  
Export : export@livpure.com

#### We Accept

* Visa
* Mastercard
* American Express
* Google Pay
* Maestro
* MobiKwik
* Paytm
* RuPay

#### CIN Number: U31100DL1994PTC061494

**Registered Address**  
Livpure Smart Homes Pvt Ltd, Plot No 221, Udhyog Vihar Phase 1, Gurgaon, Haryana, 122016 India

**Manufacturer and Packer**  
Plot No 39, Sector 4, IMT Manesar, Gurgaon, Haryana, 122050, India

#### Water Purifier in Your City

#### We Accept

* Visa
* Mastercard
* American Express
* Google Pay
* Maestro
* MobiKwik
* Paytm
* RuPay

New to Livpure ?

Create an account with us to view your order status online. Your details can also be saved for faster checkout.

[SIGN UP TODAY](javascript:void(0))

[ALREADY REGISTERED? SIGN IN](javascript:void(0))

★ Judge.me Reviews

### Let customers speak for us

87%

(3980)

10%

(443)

1%

(67)

0%

(19)

1%

(41)

P

Prabhanjan Moleyar

**Happy**

Ordered Livpure Glitz UV+UF filter by calling the number given on the product site. On the website, the product was shown as 'Sold Out' but the customer care executive was able to add to the stock and guided me through the purchase process. Apart from the tracking number provided, there were no updates for a few days, and then suddenly there was an update that the delivery would be made next day. The delivery got delayed by a day as I was not available on site, but I did not have to do any follow-up. The installation request was triggered automatically, I did not have to do anything. Again, the installation was delayed due to my unavailability, but again I did not have to do any follow-up. The system seems to have automatically escalated the delay until the installation was completed. I have used the same filter earlier. The only one negative comment I have is that the tap tends to get cut very easily, but otherwise the filter has been trouble-free.

A

Amish Kumar

**Good**

I installed it on last week of Dec 2023. Installation was quick and supportive from Livepure team. Untill now, it is working fine. I will update my review after few months based on my experience. It will be unjust to give any review without using for a significant period.

A

Anonymous

**bolt**

superb machine and services

S

SHAILESH PATEL

**EXCELLENT MATTERS**

I GET RELIEF FROM BACK PAIN, VERY COMFORT FEEL, REALLY ITS GOOD MATTERS, THANKS LIVPURE..

K

Krishna Settikere

**Pillow performance**

Very excellent product earlier i had neck problem now after using it pain subsided

Thank you for your valuable review. We are glad that you are loving our product. We would love to serve you again! Keep snoozing with us.

123

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.

×

Choose Product Buy Water Purifier

 By creating an account on Livpure, you agree to our [Privacy Policy](https://livpure.com/policies/privacy-policy), receive WhatsApp, SMS notifications or Call and consent to our cookie policy.

×

Livpure Cookies Policy
======================

Livpure will collect and use your personal data for making your product booking and for providing the services you request. During this process, we may record your preferences as well as the information about any issues you encountered during your product. Our only objective of doing this is to better meet and exceed your needs during subsequent purchasing.  
We may disclose your information to our service providers for analytical purposes so that we can better improvise your buying experience and our website facilities. Livpure has agreements to ensure confidentiality of all such information shared with service providers we work with for this purpose.  
Your personal data is kept secure. Only authorized employees, business partners, clients, contractors and other third-party providers (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.  
Livpure shall retain personal data only as long as necessary for the fulfilment of the stated purposes and should be disposed thereafter. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Please tick the boxes for your consent to the use of following personal data:

*  KYC
*  Product enhancement market feedback
*  Cookie policies
*  Customer experience
*  Support and shipping related services

All the information you give is voluntary. You have the legal right to apply for a copy of the information we hold on you and correct any inaccuracies as well as object to its use.  
You may review, update, correct or delete your personal data by e-mailing us at customercare@livpure.com. You may at any time also, contact our Data Protection Officer directly with questions and suggestions concerning data protection by e-mailing us at grievance.officer@sar-group.com  
For a full description on how we process and keep safe your personal data, please see our Privacy Policy at: [Privacy Policy](https://livpure.com/policies/privacy-policy)

Save & Continue

×

Please enter name

Name should be of 4 charector

Please enter email

Please enter valid email

Please enter phone number

Phone no should be of 10 digit

Please select product type

Select your city Bengaluru Bhopal Bhubaneswar Chandigarh Chennai Dehradun Delhi NCR Hyderabad Indore Jaipur Kanpur Kolkata Lucknow Mohali Mumbai Nagpur Panchkula Pune Raipur

By clicking Submit, you agree to our [Terms & Conditions](https://livpuresleep.com/pages/terms-condition)

Submit
